Downtown Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1926-1974, undated, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-22; 22 linear ft.; Reels 5488-5545)
  - Correspondence, Ma-Mur, undated (Reel 5489 (Box 1), Frame 306-501)
  - Correspondence, Mus-Pl, undated (Reel 5489 (Box 1), Frame 502-695)
  - Correspondence, Po-Ri, undated (Reel 5489 (Box 1), Frame 696-791)
  - Correspondence, Ro-San, undated (Reel 5489 (Box 1), Frame 792-996)
  - Correspondence, Sar-Sz, undated (Reel 5489 (Box 1), Frame 997-1223)
  - Correspondence, T, undated (Reel 5490 (Box 1), Frame 6-75)
  - Correspondence, U-Uhr, undated (Reel 5490 (Box 1), Frame 76-273)
  - Correspondence, Ull-Z, undated (Reel 5490 (Box 1), Frame 274-471)
  - Correspondence, Unidentified, and Illegible, undated (Reel 5490 (Box 1), Frame 472-662)
  - Correspondence, 1926 (Reel 5490 (Box 2), Frame 663-675)
  - Correspondence, 1927 (Reel 5490 (Box 2), Frame 676-859)
  - Correspondence, 1928 (Reel 5490 (Box 2), Frame 860-919)
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Reel 5490 (Box 2), Frame 920-1034)
  - Correspondence, 1930 (Reel 5490 (Box 2), Frame 1035-1244)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-May, 1931 (Reel 5491 (Box 2), Frame 6-201)
  - Correspondence, June-Sept., 1931 (Reel 5491 (Box 2), Frame 202-336)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec., 1931 (Reel 5491 (Box 2), Frame 337-495)
  - Correspondence, January-May, 1932 (Reel 5491 (Box 2), Frame 496-685)
  - Correspondence, June-Sept., 1932 (Reel 5491 (Box 2), Frame 686-844)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec., 1932 (Reel 5491 (Box 2), Frame 845-997)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1933 (Reel 5491 (Box 2), Frame 998-1129)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-May, 1933 (Reel 5492 (Box 2), Frame 6-205)
  - Correspondence, June-Sept., 1933 (Reel 5492 (Box 2), Frame 206-325)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec., 1933 (Reel 5492 (Box 2), Frame 326-515)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1934 (Reel 5492 (Box 2), Frame 516-712)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-Apr., 1934 (Reel 5492 (Box 2), Frame 713-883)
  - Correspondence, May-Aug., 1934 (Reel 5492 (Box 2), Frame 884-1059)
  - Correspondence, Sept.-Dec., 1934 (Reel 5492 (Box 2), Frame 1060-1241)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1935 (Reel 5493 (Box 2), Frame 6-221)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-May, 1935 (Reel 5493 (Box 2), Frame 222-406)
  - Correspondence, June-Dec., 1935 (Reel 5493 (Box 2), Frame 407-607)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-May, 1936 (Reel 5493 (Box 2), Frame 608-736)
  - Correspondence, June-Dec., 1936 (Reel 5493 (Box 2), Frame 737-843)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-June, 1937 (Reel 5493 (Box 3), Frame 844-1030)
  - Correspondence, July-Dec., 1937 (Reel 5493 (Box 3), Frame 1031-1143)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-May, 1938 (Reel 5494 (Box 3), Frame 6-157)
  - Correspondence, June-Dec., 1938 (Reel 5494 (Box 3), Frame 158-308)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Apr., 1939 (Reel 5494 (Box 3), Frame 309-493)
  - Correspondence, May-Sept., 1939 (Reel 5494 (Box 3), Frame 494-669)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec., 1939 (Reel 5494 (Box 3), Frame 670-866)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Mar., 1940 (Reel 5494 (Box 3), Frame 867-1058)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-June, 1940 (Reel 5494 (Box 3), Frame 1059-1251)
  - Correspondence, July-Oct., 1940 (Reel 5495 (Box 3), Frame 6-183)
  - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec., 1940 (Reel 5495 (Box 3), Frame 184-319)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1941 (Reel 5495 (Box 3), Frame 320-494)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-May, 1941 (Reel 5495 (Box 3), Frame 495-704)
  - Correspondence, June-July, 1941 (Reel 5495 (Box 3), Frame 705-863)
  - Correspondence, Aug.-Sept., 1941 (Reel 5495 (Box 3), Frame 864-992)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec., 1941 (Reel 5495 (Box 3), Frame 993-1299)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Mar., 1942 (Reel 5496 (Box 4), Frame 6-208)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-July, 1942 (Reel 5496 (Box 4), Frame 209-398)
  - Correspondence, Aug.-Dec., 1942 (Reel 5496 (Box 4), Frame 399-600)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Mar., 1943 (Reel 5496 (Box 4), Frame 601-778)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-Aug., 1943 (Reel 5496 (Box 4), Frame 779-963)
  - Correspondence, Sept.-Dec., 1943 (Reel 5496 (Box 4), Frame 964-1127)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Mar., 1944 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 169-339)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-July, 1944 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 6-168)
  - Correspondence, Aug.-Dec., 1944 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 522-721)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Apr., 1945 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 340-521)
  - Correspondence, May-July, 1945 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 722-890)
  - Correspondence, Aug.-Oct., 1945 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 891-1080)
  - Correspondence, Nov., 1945 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 1081-1195)
  - Correspondence, Dec., 1945 (Reel 5497 (Box 4), Frame 1196-1297)
  - Correspondence, Jan., 1946 (Reel 5498 (Box 4), Frame 6-141)
  - Correspondence, Feb.-Mar., 1946 (Reel 5498 (Box 4), Frame 142-345)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-May, 1946 (Reel 5498 (Box 4), Frame 346-507)
  - Correspondence, June-July, 1946 (Reel 5498 (Box 4), Frame 508-658)
  - Correspondence, Aug.-Sept., 1946 (Reel 5498 (Box 5), Frame 659-847)
  - Correspondence, Oct., 1946 (Reel 5498 (Box 5), Frame 848-934)
  - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec., 1946 (Reel 5498 (Box 5), Frame 935-1140)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1947 (Reel 5499 (Box 5), Frame 6-236)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-Apr., 1947 (Reel 5499 (Box 5), Frame 237-454)
  - Correspondence, May-June, 1947 (Reel 5499 (Box 5), Frame 455-661)
  - Correspondence, July-Dec., 1947 (Reel 5499 (Box 5), Frame 662-862)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1948 (Reel 5499 (Box 5), Frame 863-1010)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-May, 1948 (Reel 5499 (Box 5), Frame 1011-1202)
  - Correspondence, June-Oct., 1948 (Reel 5500 (Box 5), Frame 6-217)
  - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec., 1948 (Reel 5500 (Box 5), Frame 218-370)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Mar., 1949 (Reel 5500 (Box 5), Frame 371-584)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-June, 1949 (Reel 5500 (Box 5), Frame 585-773)
  - Correspondence, July-Sept., 1949 (Reel 5500 (Box 5), Frame 774-953)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec., 1949 (Reel 5500 (Box 5), Frame 954-1127)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1950 (Reel 5500 (Box 6), Frame 1128-1273)
  - Correspondence, Mar.-Apr., 1950 (Reel 5501 (Box 6), Frame 6-188)
  - Correspondence, May-June, 1950 (Reel 5501 (Box 6), Frame 189-380)
  - Correspondence, July-Sept., 1950 (Reel 5501 (Box 6), Frame 381-533)
  - Correspondence, Oct.-Nov., 1950 (Reel 5501 (Box 6), Frame 534-739)
  - Correspondence, Dec., 1950 (Reel 5501 (Box 6), Frame 740-817)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb., 1951 (Reel 5501 (Box 6), Frame 818-997)
  - Correspondence, Mar., 1951 (Reel 5501 (Box 6), Frame 998-1148)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-May, 1951 (Reel 5502 (Box 6), Frame 6-175)
  - Correspondence, June-Aug., 1951 (Reel 5502 (Box 6), Frame 176-324)
  - Correspondence, Sept., 1951 (Reel 5502 (Box 6), Frame 325-422)
  - Correspondence, Oct., 1951 (Reel 5502 (Box 6), Frame 423-594)
  - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec., 1951 (Reel 5502 (Box 6), Frame 595-802)
  - Correspondence, Jan., 1952 (Reel 5502 (Box 6), Frame 803-923)
  - Correspondence, Feb.-Mar., 1952 (Reel 5502 (Box 6), Frame 924-1194)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-May, 1952 (Reel 5503 (Box 6), Frame 6-230)
  - Correspondence, June, 1952 (Reel 5503 (Box 6), Frame 231-353)
  - Correspondence, July-Aug., 1952 (Reel 5503 (Box 6), Frame 354-555)
  - Correspondence, Sept., 1952 (Reel 5503 (Box 7), Frame 556-763)
  - Correspondence, Oct., 1952 (Reel 5503 (Box 7), Frame 764-990)
  - Correspondence, Nov., 1952 (Reel 5503 (Box 7), Frame 991-1200)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 1-15, 1952 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 6-160)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 16-31, 1952 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 161-277)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-14, 1953 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 278-466)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 15-31, 1953 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 467-619)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1-19, 1953 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 620-819)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 20-Mar. 17, 1953 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 820-1017)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 18-Apr. 11, 1953 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 1018-1221)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 13-30, 1953 (Reel 5504 (Box 7), Frame 1222-1357)
  - Correspondence, May, 1953 (Reel 5505 (Box 7), Frame 6-227)
  - Correspondence, June, 1953 (Reel 5505 (Box 7), Frame 228-447)
  - Correspondence, July, 1953 (Reel 5505 (Box 7), Frame 448-577)
  - Correspondence, Aug.-Sept., 1953 (Reel 5505 (Box 7), Frame 578-755)
  - Correspondence, Oct., 1953 (Reel 5505 (Box 7), Frame 756-925)
  - Correspondence, Nov., 1953 (Reel 5505 (Box 7), Frame 926-1045)
  - Correspondence, Dec., 1953 (Reel 5505 (Box 7), Frame 1046-1192)
  - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 19, 1954 (Reel 5506 (Box 8), Frame 6-196)
  - Correspondence, Feb.21-Mar., 1954 (Reel 5506 (Box 8), Frame 197-408)
  - Correspondence, Apr.-May 19, 1954 (Reel 5506 (Box 8), Frame 409-600)
  - Correspondence, May 20-June 24, 1954 (Reel 5506 (Box 8), Frame 601-803)
  - Correspondence, June 25-July 26, 1954 (Reel 5506 (Box 8), Frame 804-997)
  - Correspondence, July 27-Aug., 1954 (Reel 5506 (Box 8), Frame 998-1148)
  - Correspondence, Sept., 1954 (Reel 5506 (Box 8), Frame 1149-1315)
  - Correspondence, Oct., 1954 (Reel 5507 (Box 8), Frame 6-212)
  - Correspondence, Nov., 1954 (Reel 5507 (Box 8), Frame 213-396)
  - Correspondence, Dec., 1954 (Reel 5507 (Box 8), Frame 397-554)
  - Correspondence, Jan., 1955 (Reel 5507 (Box 8), Frame 555-773)
  - Correspondence, Feb., 1955 (Reel 5507 (Box 8), Frame 774-961)
  - Correspondence, Mar., 1955 (Reel 5507 (Box 8), Frame 962-1139)
  - Correspondence, Apr., 1955 (Reel 5507 (Box 8), Frame 1140-1316)
  - Correspondence, May, 1955 (Reel 5508 (Box 8), Frame 6-218)
  - Correspondence, June 1-27, 1955 (Reel 5508 (Box 8), Frame 219-418)
  - Correspondence, June 28-July 26, 1955 (Reel 5508 (Box 8), Frame 419-608)
  - Correspondence, July 26-Aug. 22, 1955 (Reel 5508 (Box 9), Frame 609-806)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 23-Sept. 17, 1955 (Reel 5508 (Box 9), Frame 807-1004)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 20-30, 1955 (Reel 5509 (Box 9), Frame 6-129)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 1-20, 1955 (Reel 5509 (Box 9), Frame 130-320)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 21-Nov. 12, 1955 (Reel 5509 (Box 9), Frame 321-520)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 13-Dec. 5, 1955 (Reel 5509 (Box 9), Frame 521-721)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 6-31, 1955 (Reel 5509 (Box 9), Frame 722-901)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-17, 1956 (Reel 5510 (Box 9), Frame 6-197)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 18-Feb. 14, 1956 (Reel 5510 (Box 9), Frame 198-416)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 15-29, 1956 (Reel 5510 (Box 9), Frame 417-592)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 1-19, 1956 (Reel 5510 (Box 9), Frame 593-806)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 20-31, 1956 (Reel 5510 (Box 9), Frame 807-951)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 1-13, 1956 (Reel 5510 (Box 9), Frame 952-1092)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 14-30, 1956 (Reel 5510 (Box 9), Frame 1093-1253)
  - Correspondence, May 1-24, 1956 (Reel 5511 (Box 9), Frame 6-190)
  - Correspondence, May 25-June 25, 1956 (Reel 5511 (Box 9), Frame 191-407)
  - Correspondence, June 26-July 25, 1956 (Reel 5511 (Box 9), Frame 408-595)
  - Correspondence, July 26-Aug. 30, 1956 (Reel 5511 (Box 9), Frame 596-779)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 1-21, 1956 (Reel 5511 (Box 10), Frame 780-976)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 22-Oct. 19, 1956 (Reel 5511 (Box 10), Frame 977-1167)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 20-31, 1956 (Reel 5511 (Box 10), Frame 1168-1301)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 1-22, 1956 (Reel 5512 (Box 10), Frame 6-195)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 23-Dec., 1956 (Reel 5512 (Box 10), Frame 196-402)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-14, 1957 (Reel 5512 (Box 10), Frame 403-597)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 15-31, 1957 (Reel 5512 (Box 10), Frame 598-739)
  - Correspondence, Feb., 1957 (Reel 5512 (Box 10), Frame 740-919)
  - Correspondence, Mar., 1957 (Reel 5512 (Box 10), Frame 920-1105)
  - Correspondence, Apr., 1957 (Reel 5513 (Box 10), Frame 6-194)
  - Correspondence, May, 1957 (Reel 5513 (Box 10), Frame 195-371)
  - Correspondence, June, 1957 (Reel 5513 (Box 10), Frame 372-551)
  - Correspondence, July, 1957 (Reel 5513 (Box 10), Frame 552-715)
  - Correspondence, Aug., 1957 (Reel 5513 (Box 10), Frame 716-835)
  - Correspondence, Sept., 1957 (Reel 5513 (Box 10), Frame 836-1054)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 1-14, 1957 (Reel 5513 (Box 10), Frame 1055-1202)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 15-31, 1957 (Reel 5514 (Box 10), Frame 6-140)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 1-15, 1957 (Reel 5514 (Box 11), Frame 141-315)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 16-30, 1957 (Reel 5514 (Box 11), Frame 316-459)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 1-15, 57 (Reel 5514 (Box 11), Frame 460-638)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 16-31, 1957 (Reel 5514 (Box 11), Frame 639-752)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-14, 1958 (Reel 5514 (Box 11), Frame 753-886)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 15-31, 1958 (Reel 5514 (Box 11), Frame 887-1085)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1-18, 1958 (Reel 5515 (Box 11), Frame 6-181)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 19-Mar. 9, 1958 (Reel 5515 (Box 11), Frame 182-390)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 10-31, 1958 (Reel 5515 (Box 11), Frame 391-611)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 1-23, 1958 (Reel 5515 (Box 11), Frame 612-802)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 24-May 14, 1958 (Reel 5515 (Box 11), Frame 803-1000)
  - Correspondence, May 15-31, 1958 (Reel 5515 (Box 11), Frame 1001-1155)
  - Correspondence, June 1-20, 1958 (Reel 5516 (Box 11), Frame 6-207)
  - Correspondence, June 21-July 14, 1958 (Reel 5516 (Box 11), Frame 208-401)
  - Correspondence, July 15-Aug., 1958 (Reel 5516 (Box 11), Frame 402-601)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 1-23, 1958 (Reel 5516 (Box 11), Frame 602-798)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 24-Oct. 16, 1958 (Reel 5516 (Box 11), Frame 799-997)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 17-31, 1958 (Reel 5516 (Box 12), Frame 998-1119)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 1-17, 1958 (Reel 5517 (Box 12), Frame 6-170)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 18-Dec. 8, 1958 (Reel 5517 (Box 12), Frame 171-375)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 9-31, 1958 (Reel 5517 (Box 12), Frame 376-588)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-10, 1959 (Reel 5517 (Box 12), Frame 589-720)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 11-31, 1959 (Reel 5517 (Box 12), Frame 721-923)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1-17, 1959 (Reel 5517 (Box 12), Frame 924-1128)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 18-28, 1959 (Reel 5517 (Box 12), Frame 1129-1261)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 1-18, 1959 (Reel 5518 (Box 12), Frame 6-204)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 19-Apr. 10, 1959 (Reel 5518 (Box 12), Frame 205-401)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 11-30, 1959 (Reel 5518 (Box 12), Frame 402-610)
  - Correspondence, May 1-19, 1959 (Reel 5518 (Box 12), Frame 611-820)
  - Correspondence, May 20-June 16, 1959 (Reel 5518 (Box 12), Frame 821-1034)
  - Correspondence, June 17-30, 1959 (Reel 5518 (Box 12), Frame 1035-1201)
  - Correspondence, July, 1959 (Reel 5519 (Box 12), Frame 6-209)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 3-Sept. 14, 1959 (Reel 5519 (Box 12), Frame 210-378)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 15-30, 1959 (Reel 5519 (Box 12), Frame 379-595)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 1-23, 1959 (Reel 5519 (Box 13), Frame 596-798)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 24-Nov. 8, 1959 (Reel 5519 (Box 13), Frame 799-979)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 9-31, 1959 (Reel 5519 (Box 13), Frame 980-1154)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 1-15, 1959 (Reel 5520 (Box 13), Frame 6-141)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 16-31, 1959 (Reel 5520 (Box 13), Frame 142-267)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-18, 1960 (Reel 5520 (Box 13), Frame 268-476)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 19-Feb. 5, 1960 (Reel 5520 (Box 13), Frame 477-675)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 6-24, 1960 (Reel 5520 (Box 13), Frame 676-868)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 25-Mar. 14, 1960 (Reel 5520 (Box 13), Frame 869-1067)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 15-31, 1960 (Reel 5520 (Box 13), Frame 1068-1254)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 1-19, 1960 (Reel 5521 (Box 13), Frame 6-209)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 20-May 10, 1960 (Reel 5521 (Box 13), Frame 210-415)
  - Correspondence, May 11-27, 1960 (Reel 5521 (Box 13), Frame 416-613)
  - Correspondence, May 28-June 15, 1960 (Reel 5521 (Box 13), Frame 614-807)
  - Correspondence, June 16-July 9, 1960 (Reel 5521 (Box 13), Frame 808-1106)
  - Correspondence, July 10-31, 1960 (Reel 5521 (Box 13), Frame 1107-1199)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 1-24, 1960 (Reel 5522 (Box 13), Frame 6-199)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 25-Sept. 17, 1960 (Reel 5522 (Box 14), Frame 200-406)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 18-Oct. 9, 1960 (Reel 5522 (Box 14), Frame 407-595)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 10-25, 1960 (Reel 5522 (Box 14), Frame 596-789)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 26-Nov. 13, 1960 (Reel 5522 (Box 14), Frame 790-981)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 14-Dec. 14, 1960 (Reel 5522 (Box 14), Frame 982-1188)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 5-15, 1960 (Reel 5522 (Box 14), Frame 1189-1302)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 16-31, 1960 (Reel 5523 (Box 14), Frame 6-143)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-17, 1961 (Reel 5523 (Box 14), Frame 144-335)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 18-Feb. 3, 1961 (Reel 5523 (Box 14), Frame 336-537)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 4-24, 1961 (Reel 5523 (Box 14), Frame 538-738)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 25-Mar. 14, 1961 (Reel 5523 (Box 14), Frame 739-944)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 15-28, 1961 (Reel 5523 (Box 14), Frame 945-1141)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 29-Apr. 14, 1961 (Reel 5523 (Box 14), Frame 1142-1327)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 15-May 2, 1961 (Reel 5524 (Box 14), Frame 6-196)
  - Correspondence, May 3-20, 1961 (Reel 5524 (Box 14), Frame 197-405)
  - Correspondence, May 21-June 8, 1961 (Reel 5524 (Box 14), Frame 406-601)
  - Correspondence, June 9-30, 1961 (Reel 5524 (Box 14), Frame 602-801)
  - Correspondence, July 1-20, 1961 (Reel 5524 (Box 15), Frame 802-992)
  - Correspondence, July 21-31, 1961 (Reel 5524 (Box 15), Frame 993-1083)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 1-16, 1961 (Reel 5524 (Box 15), Frame 1084-1243)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 17-Sept. 8, 1961 (Reel 5525 (Box 15), Frame 6-207)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 9-25, 1961 (Reel 5525 (Box 15), Frame 208-402)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 26-Oct. 14, 1961 (Reel 5525 (Box 15), Frame 403-613)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 15-28, 1961 (Reel 5525 (Box 15), Frame 614-823)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 30-Nov. 14, 1961 (Reel 5525 (Box 15), Frame 824-1034)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 15-30, 1961 (Reel 5525 (Box 15), Frame 1035-1242)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 1-14, 1961 (Reel 5526 (Box 15), Frame 6-186)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 15-31, 1961 (Reel 5526 (Box 15), Frame 187-353)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-12, 1962 (Reel 5526 (Box 15), Frame 354-542)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 13-29, 1962 (Reel 5526 (Box 15), Frame 543-746)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 30-Feb. 13, 1962 (Reel 5526 (Box 15), Frame 747-953)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 14-28, 1962 (Reel 5526 (Box 15), Frame 954-1126)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 1-14, 1962 (Reel 5526 (Box 15), Frame 1127-1286)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 15-28, 1962 (Reel 5527 (Box 15), Frame 6-190)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 29-Apr. 17, 1962 (Reel 5527 (Box 16), Frame 191-392)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 18-May 8, 1962 (Reel 5527 (Box 16), Frame 393-602)
  - Correspondence, May 9-29, 1962 (Reel 5527 (Box 16), Frame 603-804)
  - Correspondence, May 30-June 15, 1962 (Reel 5527 (Box 16), Frame 805-1003)
  - Correspondence, June 16-30, 1962 (Reel 5527 (Box 16), Frame 1004-1172)
  - Correspondence, July 1-22, 1962 (Reel 5528 (Box 16), Frame 6-204)
  - Correspondence, July 23-Aug. 20, 1962 (Reel 5528 (Box 16), Frame 205-404)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 20-Sept. 19, 1962 (Reel 5528 (Box 16), Frame 405-603)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 19-Oct. 10, 1962 (Reel 5528 (Box 16), Frame 604-805)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 11-29, 1962 (Reel 5528 (Box 16), Frame 806-1003)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 29-Nov. 15, 1962 (Reel 5528 (Box 16), Frame 1004-1221)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 16-30, 1962 (Reel 5529 (Box 16), Frame 6-169)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 30-Dec. 12, 1962 (Reel 5529 (Box 16), Frame 170-350)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 13-31, 1962 (Reel 5529 (Box 16), Frame 351-502)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-15, 1963 (Reel 5529 (Box 16), Frame 503-687)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 15-29, 1963 (Reel 5529 (Box 16), Frame 688-875)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 29-Feb. 13, 1963 (Reel 5529 (Box 17), Frame 876-1059)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 13-28, 1963 (Reel 5529 (Box 17), Frame 1060-1239)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 1-16, 1963 (Reel 5530 (Box 17), Frame 6-186)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 16-29, 1963 (Reel 5530 (Box 17), Frame 187-372)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 29-Apr. 12, 1963 (Reel 5530 (Box 17), Frame 373-558)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 12-30, 1963 (Reel 5530 (Box 17), Frame 559-743)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 30-May 14, 1963 (Reel 5530 (Box 17), Frame 744-930)
  - Correspondence, May 14-31, 1963 (Reel 5530 (Box 17), Frame 931-1113)
  - Correspondence, June 1-20, 1963 (Reel 5531 (Box 17), Frame 6-188)
  - Correspondence, June 20-July 10, 1963 (Reel 5531 (Box 17), Frame 189-376)
  - Correspondence, July 10-Aug. 2, 1963 (Reel 5531 (Box 17), Frame 377-564)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 2-Sept. 11, 1963 (Reel 5531 (Box 17), Frame 565-752)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 11-30, 1963 (Reel 5531 (Box 17), Frame 753-940)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 30-Oct. 16, 1963 (Reel 5531 (Box 17), Frame 941-1125)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 17-Nov. 1, 1963 (Reel 5532 (Box 17), Frame 6-184)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 1-18, 1963 (Reel 5532 (Box 17), Frame 185-369)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 18-Dec. 8, 1963 (Reel 5532 (Box 17), Frame 370-554)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 9-31, 1963 (Reel 5532 (Box 17), Frame 555-740)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-14, 1964 (Reel 5532 (Box 18), Frame 741-904)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 14-30, 1964 (Reel 5532 (Box 18), Frame 905-1070)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 30-Feb. 12, 1964 (Reel 5532 (Box 18), Frame 1071-1228)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 13-Mar. 3, 1964 (Reel 5533 (Box 18), Frame 6-196)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 3-19, 1964 (Reel 5533 (Box 18), Frame 197-393)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 19-Apr. 6, 1964 (Reel 5533 (Box 18), Frame 394-590)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 6-24, 1964 (Reel 5533 (Box 18), Frame 591-787)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 24-May 12, 1964 (Reel 5533 (Box 18), Frame 788-984)
  - Correspondence, May 12-31, 1964 (Reel 5533 (Box 18), Frame 985-1177)
  - Correspondence, June 1-17, 1964 (Reel 5534 (Box 18), Frame 6-209)
  - Correspondence, June 17-July 6, 1964 (Reel 5534 (Box 18), Frame 210-418)
  - Correspondence, July 6-28, 1964 (Reel 5534 (Box 18), Frame 419-627)
  - Correspondence, July 28-Sept. 2, 1964 (Reel 5534 (Box 18), Frame 628-838)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 2-28, 1964 (Reel 5534 (Box 18), Frame 839-1048)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 28-Oct. 16, 1964 (Reel 5534 (Box 18), Frame 1049-1255)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 17-Nov. 4, 1964 (Reel 5535 (Box 19), Frame 6-208)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 4-24, 1964 (Reel 5535 (Box 19), Frame 209-416)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 24-Dec. 10, 1964 (Reel 5535 (Box 19), Frame 417-624)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 11-31, 1964 (Reel 5535 (Box 19), Frame 625-831)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-9, 1965 (Reel 5535 (Box 19), Frame 832-936)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 9-20, 1965 (Reel 5535 (Box 19), Frame 937-1041)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 20-31, 1965 (Reel 5535 (Box 19), Frame 1042-1143)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 1-18, 1965 (Reel 5536 (Box 19), Frame 6-194)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 18-Mar. 12, 1965 (Reel 5536 (Box 19), Frame 195-389)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 12-31, 1965 (Reel 5536 (Box 19), Frame 390-584)
  - Correspondence, Mar. 31-Apr. 21, 1965 (Reel 5536 (Box 19), Frame 585-780)
  - Correspondence, Apr. 22-May 20, 1965 (Reel 5536 (Box 19), Frame 781-975)
  - Correspondence, May 20-June 15, 1965 (Reel 5536 (Box 19), Frame 976-1167)
  - Correspondence, June 14-July 2, 1965 (Reel 5537 (Box 19), Frame 6-194)
  - Correspondence, July 2-Aug. 4, 1965 (Reel 5537 (Box 19), Frame 195-388)
  - Correspondence, Aug. 4-Sept. 10, 1965 (Reel 5537 (Box 19), Frame 389-583)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 11-16, 1965 (Reel 5537 (Box 19), Frame 584-781)
  - Correspondence, Sept. 16-Oct. 4, 1965 (Reel 5537 (Box 20), Frame 782-979)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 4-18, 1965 (Reel 5537 (Box 20), Frame 980-1107)
  - Correspondence, Oct. 19-Nov. 11, 1965 (Reel 5538 (Box 20), Frame 6-213)
  - Correspondence, Nov. 11-Dec. 7, 1965 (Reel 5538 (Box 20), Frame 214-426)
  - Correspondence, Dec. 7-31, 1965 (Reel 5538 (Box 20), Frame 427-642)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 1-25, 1966 (Reel 5538 (Box 20), Frame 643-843)
  - Correspondence, Jan. 25-Feb. 23, 1966 (Reel 5538 (Box 20), Frame 844-1043)
  - Correspondence, Feb. 23-Mar. 14, 1966 (Reel 5538 (Box 20), Frame 1044-1232)